short-funny-quotes.com 2017-11-26

# Short Funny Quotes - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us. 

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit us, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Voluntary Disclosure  
You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards, chat areas, comments sections or simliar areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of us and this policy. 

All our visitor information is held in strict confidence. If you choose to join our mailing list we do not sell or share our customer list with any other entities. We may on occasion send you messages with product offers or links to websites. You can op-out of the mailling list at any time. 

We cannot be responsible for the policies or content of other sites, even if we link to them.
